RG 071, Department of Housing
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Deputy Commissioner, 1978-1990; 38 cubic feet
  - Subject Files
    - David W. Deakin, 1978-1988; 1989-008; 21 cubic feet
      - Subject Files (Box 20)
        - Housing projects in planning, status (Box 23)
        - Income limits, Rental Homes for elderly (Box 23)
        - Insurance (Box 23)
        - Internal Auditor (Box 23)
        - Invitations (Box 23)
        - Insurance, 1987 (Box 23)
        - Unlabeled file (Box 23)
        - Kensington square II (Box 23)
        - La Casa de Puerto Rico (Box 23)
        - Land use report (Box 23)
        - Legislation, 1982-1989; 8 folders (Box 24)
        - Legislative Program review and Investigations committee (Box 24)
        - Legislation, 1979 (Box 24)
        - Legislation on Planning Development (Box 24)
        - Local housing Authorities, insurance, master policies (Box 24)
        - Local Housing Authorities, waiting lists (Box 24)
        - Long range data processing planning (Box 24)
        - Long term care commission (Box 24)
        - Lt. Governor report (Box 24)
        - Management (Box 24)
        - Mr. Zachos, management (Box 24)
        - Management advisory council (Box 24)
        - Management information section (Box 24)
        - Management update (Box 24)
        - Manger's meetings (Box 24)
        - MATEP Manual (Box 24)
        - M.I.P. (Box 24)
        - March (Box 24)
        - Milano, Anthony V. secretary, OPM (Box 24)
        - Minority Hiring (Box 24)
        - Mobile home parks (Box 24)
        - Mobile Home Task Force (Box 24)
        - MR Affordable Housing (Box 24)
        - Moderate Rental project disposition (Box 24)
        - Moderate rental Regulations, revised (Box 24)
        - M.R. Regulations (Box 24)
        - Moderate Rental Rehab, proposed (Box 25)
        - Moderate rental (Box 25)
        - M-R sales (Box 25)
        - Monthly Housing Permits (Box 25)
        - Multi-family Development (Box 25)
        - Municipal Housing Trust Fund (Box 25)
        - Mutual Housing (Box 25)
        - Conn NAHRO (Box 25)
        - NAHRO (Box 25)
        - Naugatuck MR 61 (Box 25)
        - Northern Connecticut Community development corporation (Box 25)
        - Neighborhood housing services (Box 25)
        - Neighborhood facilities (Box 25)
        - Neighborhood rehab (Box 25)
        - New Britain Re-Hab (Box 25)
        - Mobile Homes (Box 25)
        - New Haven conversion (Box 25)
        - New Haven, HSD, Bristol street (Box 25)
        - New Haven Recievership (Box 25)
        - Neighborhood re-hab Plainville (Box 25)
        - News Clippings (Box 25)
        - Norwalk rehab (Box 25)
        - Norwich diocese congregate Housing (Box 25)
        - OPM, Misc. Correspondence (Box 25)
        - M. R. Program Orfino Project (Box 25)
        - John F. Papandrea (Box 25)
        - Personnel material (Box 25)
        - Pilot (Box 25)
        - Planning (Box 25)
        - Planning, Development session, 1980 (Box 25)
        - Plan review section (Box 25)
        - Policies and procedures (Box 25)
        - policy and planning personell (Box 25)
        - Position classifications (Box 25)
        - Press releases (Box 25)
        - President's commission on Housing (Box 25)
        - Procedure execution of contracts (Box 25)
        - Procedures manual (Box 25)
        - Program budgeting (Box 25)
        - Program status reports (Box 25)
        - Programs fundings, N.R. Elderly, M.R., Infill, ect. (Box 25)
        - Project reports (Box 25)
        - Property Insurance, municipal Housing Authorities (Box 25)
        - Proposed regulations, rental structure income limits (Box 26)
        - Proposed Job specification revisions, new job specifications (Box 26)
        - Proposed sale of project notes (Box 26)
        - Public Housing manager certification program (Box 26)
        - Publications (Box 26)
        - Status report on progress of projects in planning (Box 26)
        - Public acts (Box 26)
        - Public Act 80-449, discriminating against families renting with children (Box 26)
        - Public safety, Department (Box 26)
        - Quinebaug Congregate (Box 26)
        - DOH, regulation, 1987 (Box 26)
        - Relaocation, Town of Vernon (Box 26)
        - Rental assistance (Box 26)
        - Rehabilitation (Box 26)
        - Regional Housing Council (Box 26)
        - DOH regulations (Box 26)
        - Rental subsidy pilot program (Box 26)
        - Reorganization (Box 26)
        - Revoling Fund, receivership (Box 26)
        - Second mortgage (Box 26)
        - Section 8 programs (Box 26)
        - Senate Bill (Box 26)
        - Senate Bill 7113 Public act No. 81-400 (Box 26)
        - Section 8 study (Box 26)
        - Senator Audrey Beck (Box 26)
        - Senior Executive service (Box 26)
        - Sheldon Oak, 1986 (Box 26)
        - Single-family Home, existing (Box 26)
        - Sinking Fund Treasurer's (Box 26)
        - Putnam, small cities, 1986 (Box 26)
        - Small Cities, 1987 (Box 26)
        - Sasco Creek Village (Box 26)
        - Small cities, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - SMSA, Income Limits (Box 26)
        - Solar Bank Program (Box 26)
        - Stamford, congregate Housing (Box 26)
        - State Rural development council (Box 26)
        - Status reports, 1984 (Box 26)
        - Stockton, Edward, commissioner, DED (Box 26)
        - Sunrise Ridge condominiums (Box 26)
        - SWERPA (Box 26)
        - Syndication (Box 26)
        - Unlabeled file (Box 26)
        - Tax abatement (Box 26)
        - Time sheets (Box 26)
        - Three year Housing advisory plan (Box 26)
        - Three Year Plan (Box 26)
          - Task Force Recommendation, 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Three Year Housing Plan (Box 26)
        - TPA Services (Box 26)
        - Travel, Mileage (Box 26)
        - Travel activities, directors from MTD (Box 26)
        - Windsor Locks, Tornado victims (Box 26)
        - New Program, Transitional Housing, 1985 (Box 26)
        - Travel, Washington (Box 26)
        - Tri-State (Box 26)
        - United Fund (Box 26)
        - Upper Albany (Box 26)
        - Urban Act, joint funding (Box 26)
        - Urban Homesteading (Box 26)
        - Urban renewal (Box 26)
        - DOH, workshops, nuts and bolts (Box 26)
        - Vactions and vacation carry over (Box 26)
        - Vincent, The (Box 26)
        - 95 Vine street (Box 26)
        - Weatherization (Box 26)
        - Wilton, moderate cost Housing, 1986 (Box 26)
        - Yankee Mac (Box 26)
      - City Files (Box 26)
        - Ansonia (Box 26)
        - Beacon falls (Box 26)
        - Berlin (Box 26)
        - Bethel (Box 26)
        - Brandford (Box 27)
        - Bridgeport (Box 27)
        - Bristol (Box 27)
        - Brooklyn (Box 27)
        - Brookfield (Box 27)
        - Canton (Box 27)
        - Cheshire (Box 27)
        - Clinton (Box 27)
        - Colchester (Box 27)
        - Conventry (Box 27)
        - Danbury (Box 27)
        - Derby, 3 folders (Box 27)
        - East Hampton (Box 27)
        - East Hartford (Box 27)
        - East Haven (Box 27)
        - East Lyme (Box 27)
        - East Windsor (Box 27)
        - Ellington (Box 27)
        - Enfield (Box 27)
        - Essex (Box 27)
        - Fairfield (Box 27)
        - Fairfield, Sunny Ridge (Box 27)
        - Farmington (Box 27)
        - Franklin (Box 27)
        - Glastonbury (Box 27)
        - Greenwich (Box 27)
        - Griswold (Box 27)
        - Groton (Box 27)
        - Guilford (Box 27)
        - Hamden (Box 27)
        - Hebron (Box 27)
        - Hartford (Box 27)
        - Killingly (Box 27)
        - Ledyard (Box 27)
        - Litchfield (Box 27)
        - Manchester (Box 27)
        - Mansfield (Box 27)
        - Meriden (Box 27)
        - Middlefield (Box 27)
        - Middletown (Box 27)
        - Milford (Box 27)
        - Monroe (Box 27)
        - Montville (Box 27)
        - Morris (Box 27)
        - Naugatuck (Box 27)
        - New Britain (Box 27)
        - New Canaan (Box 28)
        - New Haven (Box 28)
        - New London (Box 28)
        - Newington (Box 28)
        - North branford (Box 28)
        - North Canaan (Box 28)
        - North Haven (Box 28)
        - Norwalk (Box 28)
        - Norwich (Box 28)
        - Plainfield (Box 28)
        - Planville (Box 28)
        - Plymouth (Box 28)
        - Portland (Box 28)
        - Preston (Box 28)
        - Putnam (Box 28)
        - Redding Housing Authority (Box 28)
        - Rocky Hill (Box 28)
        - Ridgefield (Box 28)
        - Rockville (Box 28)
        - Rocky Hill, H.A. (Box 28)
        - Seymour (Box 28)
        - Shelton (Box 28)
        - Simsbury (Box 28)
        - Somers (Box 28)
        - Southbury (Box 28)
        - South Windsor (Box 28)
        - Southington (Box 28)
        - Sprague (Box 28)
        - Stamford (Box 28)
        - Stafford (Box 28)
        - Stonington (Box 28)
        - Stratford (Box 28)
        - Suffield (Box 28)
        - Thomaston (Box 28)
        - Thompson (Box 28)
        - Tolland (Box 28)
        - Torrington (Box 28)
        - Trumbull (Box 28)
        - Voluntown (Box 28)
        - Wallingford (Box 28)
        - Waterbury (Box 28)
        - Watertown (Box 28)
        - West Hartford (Box 28)
        - West Haven (Box 28)
        - Westport, H.A., M.R.D. (Box 28)
        - Westport (Box 28)
        - Wethersfield (Box 28)
        - Willimantic (Box 28)
        - Winchester (Box 28)
        - Windsor (Box 28)
        - Windsor Locks (Box 28)
        - Woodstock (Box 28)
        - Wolcott (Box 28)
      - Administration Files (Box 29)
        - Capital Housing, 1986 (Box 29)
        - Administrative Procedures, 1980 (Box 29)
        - DOH Audit (Box 29)
        - Low income Housing (Box 29)
        - Fire Safety, L.H.A. management (Box 29)
        - Administration, 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box 29)
        - Development, guide for project manuals TPA (Box 29)
        - Eastern Tour, Ted Fusaro (Box 29)
        - Interdepartmental messages, 5 inches (Box 29)
      - Appropriations, Bond Commission Files (Box 30)
        - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box 30)
        - Monthly analysis of Appropriations, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
        - Appropriation requirements, 1982-1983 (Box 30)
        - Application, agreements approved, 1982 (Box 30)
        - Appropriation subcommittee Hearing, 1982 February 24 (Box 30)
        - Monthly analysis, appropriations requirements, 1981 (Box 30)
        - Application, agreements approved, weekly reports, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 30)
        - Appropriations committee (Box 30)
        - Budget, FY 88-89 (Box 30)
        - Directors meetings (Box 30)
        - Bond commission, 1979-1984; 28 folders (Box 30)
      - Bonding Information, 9 folders (27 inches) (Box 31)
      - Bonding Information, 3 folders (3 inches) (Box 32)
    - Victor Cruse, 1981-1986; 12 cubic feet
      - T003128, 11 cubic feet
        - Acquistion of housing loans (Box 1)
        - Administration (Box 1)
          - Personnel- Job descriptions, 1 folder (4 inches) (Box 1)
          - Financial Statements (Box 2)
        - Administrative Services (Box 2)
        - Affirmative Action, 1 folder (4 inches) (Box 2)
        - Applications/Agreements approved (Box 3)
        - Appropriations (Box 3)
        - Archdiocese of Hartford (Box 3)
        - Asylum Hill organizing project (Box 3)
        - Attorney General (Box 3)
        - Attorneys for closings, fees, legal services, ect. (Box 3)
        - Audit problems (Box 3)
        - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box 3)
        - Bond Commission (Box 3)
        - Bond Funds, Unallocated elderly and congregate (Box 3)
        - Boston Compact, Executive Summary (Box 3)
        - Bridgeport, Smith Street (Box 3)
        - Budget, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 3)
        - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
        - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
        - Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
        - Budget, Fiscal, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
        - Canale, Misc. Correspondence, 1 folder ( 3 inches) (Box 4)
        - Cauncey Harris, Family Housing (Box 4)
        - Central Housing Committee, 1981 (Box 4)
        - Central Housing Committee, Central Housing Conference, 1982 (Box 4)
        - Central Housing Committee, 1983; 4 folders (Box 4)
        - Central Housing Committee, 1985 (Box 4)
        - Cheshire Housing Authority (Box 4)
        - Connecticut Housing finance Authority, Operating manual (Box 4)
        - CHFA (Box 4)
          - News release (Box 5)
          - Connecticut Housing Investment Fund (Box 5)
        - CHIF, VRC (Box 5)
        - Citibank (Box 5)
        - Citizen's Advisory Council (Box 5)
        - Clay Hill (Box 5)
        - Collaboration for Connecticut's Training Institute (Box 5)
        - CCDA, Community Development (Box 5)
        - Community Housing, Development Corporation (Box 5)
        - Condo conversions (Box 5)
        - Conference, Handi-Tap seminar, October 21-23 (Box 5)
        - Congregate Conference, 1985 April 24 (Box 5)
        - Congregate Housing (Box 6)
        - Congregate Housing, CHA (Box 6)
        - Congregate Task force, Study (Box 6)
        - Connecticut conference on Municipalities (Box 6)
        - Connecticut Association for Community Action, 2 folders (Box 6)
        - Connecticut Legal Services (Box 6)
        - Connecticut Social Welfare, Conference (Box 6)
        - Construction Activity Report (Box 6)
        - Contracts/Applications (Box 6)
        - Cooperative Housing (Box 6)
        - COSCAA (Box 6)
        - Council and Voluntary Action (Box 6)
        - George Crawford, Law Office (Box 6)
        - CRCOG (Box 6)
        - Criminal Justice Information (Box 6)
        - Corporation for Technical Assistance to Neighborhoods of Hartford (Box 6)
        - CUES (Box 6)
        - Data Sheets programs (Box 6)
        - Department of Administrative sevices (Box 6)
        - DOH (Box 6)
          - Audit (Box 6)
          - Funding (Box 6)
          - Housing Manual (Box 6)
          - Misc. (Box 6)
        - Developers (Box 6)
        - Development Block Grants (Box 6)
        - Downpayment Assistance program (Box 7)
        - DPAP, Attorneys (Box 7)
        - Taskforce, Homeless (Box 7)
        - Development Division, 1 folder ( 3 inches) (Box 7)
        - Dwelling Development Corporation (Box 7)
        - East Hartford Housing Authority, Duffy, Misc. Correspondence (Box 8)
        - East Main Street, Revitalization (Box 8)
        - Eastern Area Advisory Council (Box 8)
        - Eastern Connecticut, Advisory Commission (Box 8)
        - E.C.L.P. Loan Appropriations (Box 8)
        - Educational Properties (Box 8)
        - EEO (Box 8)
        - Elderly Housing (Box 8)
        - EL Hogar Del Futuro (Box 8)
        - Eminent Domain (Box 8)
        - Energy and Public (Box 8)
        - Energy Programs (Box 8)
        - Enviromental Classification, 3 folders (Box 8)
        - Ethics Commission (Box 8)
        - Executive Order #1 (Box 8)
        - Executive Order #15, Revised draft (Box 8)
        - Existing Housing (Box 8)
        - Fair Housing/ Fair Rent Commissions (Box 8)
        - Fairfield Project (Box 8)
        - Fairmont Heights (Box 8)
        - Federal Audit (Box 8)
        - FEMA (Box 8)
        - Finance Advisory Committee (Box 9)
        - Finance Committee, Legal services training (Box 9)
        - Finance, Revenue and Bonding Commission (Box 9)
        - Financial Statements and Supplemental Data (Box 9)
        - Finch, Bill (Box 9)
        - Flex-time program (Box 9)
        - Flood Relief, Housing (Box 9)
        - Flood Relief, Program (Box 9)
        - Fusaro, Misc. Correspondence (Box 9)
        - Futures (Box 9)
        - Futures, Committee (Box 9)
        - General Assembly, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - General contractors (Box 9)
        - General letters (Box 9)
        - General statutes (Box 9)
        - Government clippings (Box 9)
        - Governor O"Neill employee suggestion (Box 9)
        - Governor's bi-weekly report, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Granny Flats Forum (Box 9)
        - Greater Bridgeport Regional Housing Council (Box 9)
        - Greenwich audit (Box 9)
        - Griswold Litigation E-111 (Box 9)
        - Haley Manor- Board of Directors (Box 9)
        - Handicapped housing (Box 9)
        - Robert Hardiman (Box 9)
        - Hartford Black Democratic Club (Box 10)
        - Hartford, City of (Box 10)
        - Hartford Component, Hartford Comprehsensive plan of Development (Box 10)
        - Hartford, Conn. Council of the National Council of Negro Women (Box 10)
        - Hartford Human Relations Commission (Box 10)
        - HDC Programs Contract, ETC (Box 10)
        - Hesse, Mr. (Box 10)
        - Higher education (Box 10)
        - Task Force, Home equity (Box 10)
        - HUD (Box 10)
        - Housing and Urban Development, Task Force (Box 10)
        - Housing Authority legal problems (Box 10)
        - Housing Coalition (Box 10)
        - Housing Coalition for the Capital Region, INC. (Box 10)
        - Housing code inspection (Box 10)
        - Housing Education Resource Center (Box 10)
        - Housing newsletter (Box 10)
        - Housing Programs, Hispanic Community (Box 10)
        - Housing Task Force (Box 10)
        - Housing Task Force, Blue Ribbon Committee (Box 10)
        - Housing Trust Fund, 1984 (Box 10)
        - HSD Programs (Box 10)
        - Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 10)
        - Human Services (Box 10)
        - Imagineers, Inc. (Box 10)
        - Income limits (Box 10)
        - Incoming Interdepartment memorandum (Box 10)
        - Infill Housing, 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Internal Audit Reports (Box 10)
        - Job sites (Box 10)
        - Jobs Act, 1983 (Box 10)
        - Kensington Square II (Box 10)
        - La Casa De Puerto Rico (Box 11)
        - Lamb, Misc. correspondence (Box 11)
        - Landlord/Tenant (Box 11)
        - Land use (Box 11)
        - Mr. Lash (Box 11)
        - League of Women Voters of Connecticut, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Legal Assistance and Relocation Appeals (Box 11)
        - Legal opinions (Box 11)
        - Legal Service Training and Advocacy Project, Inc. (Box 11)
        - Legal Technical Assistance Corporation (Box 11)
        - Legislation, 1983 (Box 11)
        - Housing legislation, 1981 (Box 11)
        - Legislation, Implementation 1981 legislation (Box 11)
        - Proposed legislation (Box 11)
        - Legislative calendar (Box 11)
        - Legislative Regulation Review Committee (Box 11)
        - Legislative review, Sunset (Box 11)
        - Legislature, 1985; 1 folder ( 3 inches) (Box 12)
        - Long range data processing, 2 folder (Box 12)
        - Law and moderate income (Box 12)
        - Low income planning agency (Box 12)
        - Lyons, A. Bates, OPM (Box 12)
        - Management Advisory Council (Box 12)
        - Management Division, 1 folder ( 3 inches) (Box 13)
        - Management information, 1 folder ( 3 inches) (Box 13)
        - Management update (Box 14)
        - March, Inc. (Box 14)
        - Market study report (Box 14)
        - Mechanics Lien, New Haven (Box 14)
        - Mental Health (Box 14)
        - Department of Mental Health (Box 14)
        - Merit Promotional Plan (Box 14)
        - Merit Promotional System (Box 14)
        - Ministerial alliance (Box 14)
        - MIP (Box 14)
        - Misc. correspondence State Senators and Representatives (Box 14)
        - Moderate Rental Housing Regulation (Box 14)
        - Multi-Family Housing Development (Box 14)
        - Milano, Anthony V. OPM (Box 14)
        - Misc. newsletters (Box 14)
        - Mobile homes (Box 14)
        - Moderate Rental Program, 1984 (Box 14)
        - Monthy analysis of appropriation requirements (Box 14)
        - Mortgage and real estate (Box 14)
        - Mortgage Finance Division (Box 14)
        - Mortgages (Box 14)
        - Multi-Family status report (Box 15)
        - Multi-Family Urban homesteading (Box 15)
        - NAHRO (Box 15)
        - NAHRO, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
        - NAHRO, DOH Organization, Slayton (Box 15)
        - NAHRO, Legislative Update Ect. (Box 15)
        - NAACP (Box 15)
        - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Box 15)
        - National Hispanic Coalition (Box 15)
        - National Incorporation of Tentants (N.I.T) Inc. (Box 15)
        - National Institute of Building Science (Box 15)
        - Neighborhood Housing Service (Box 15)
        - Neighborhood Rehabilitation funding recommendations (Box 15)
        - New Britan Housing Authority (Box 15)
        - Examiner's Report New Britain Housing Authority (Box 15)
        - New Haven McConaughy Terrace (Box 15)
        - New Haven, Neighborhood Housing Service (Box 15)
        - Newbury Commons (Box 15)
        - Newsletter, Department of Housing (Box 15)
        - NOLPE - 1981, Annual convention (Box 15)
        - North Branford Housing Authority (Box 15)
        - One stop application (Box 16)
        - OPM correspondence (Box 16)
        - Parents Anonymous for Connecticut (Box 16)
        - Park Street (Box 16)
        - Personnel changes (Box 16)
        - Personnel, Handbook supervisors (Box 16)
        - Pilot (Box 16)
        - Pilot Modular project progress report (Box 16)
        - Pilot payments, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
        - Plan Review section (Box 16)
        - Planning and Development (Box 16)
        - Planning and Development Committee (Box 16)
        - Planning and Development Testimony, JEC (Box 16)
        - Planning and research (Box 16)
        - Portland Housing Authority (Box 16)
        - President's Commission on Housing (Box 17)
        - President's State of the Union address (Box 17)
        - Projects in Planning (Box 17)
        - Projects on Planning (Box 17)
        - Promotional/ New hires (Box 17)
        - Public Housing Corporation, 2 folders (Box 17)
        - Publicly assisted housing (Box 17)
        - Purchase requisitions (Box 17)
        - Quarterly housing status reports, 1983 December 31 (Box 17)
        - Quebec Square Housing, Inc. (Box 17)
        - Receivership, Revolving fund (Box 17)
        - Regional Housing Council (Box 17)
        - Regional Plan Association (Box 17)
        - Relocation, Benjamin, 4 folders (Box 17)
        - Rent subsidy (Box 18)
        - Rental assistance program (Box 18)
        - Rental projects and assignments (Box 18)
        - Rental Rehab Program (Box 18)
        - Reorganization (Box 18)
        - Research consultant (Box 18)
        - Revised rental structure and new income limits (Box 18)
        - Robinwood (Box 18)
        - MR. Rothstein, Oakland Heights (Box 18)
        - SAND (Box 18)
        - Secretary of the State (Box 18)
        - Section 8 Audit, 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Section 8 Housing Assistance payments contracts (Box 18)
        - Security Deposits, emergency shelters (Box 18)
        - Senate Bills (Box 18)
        - Seymore Housing Authority (Box 18)
        - Sheldon Oak Central, Inc. (Box 18)
        - Small cities, 1984; 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Small cities, 1985 (Box 19)
        - Southwest Area Advisory Council (Box 19)
        - Speaking engagements (Box 19)
        - Special act 80-51 (Box 19)
        - State funding to Connecticut Towns and Cities report, 1977-1986 (Box 19)
        - State of Connecticut House of Representatives (Box 19)
        - State of Connecticut Senate (Box 19)
        - Staus report (Box 19)
        - Summit meeting, 1982 March 29-30 (Box 19)
        - Supervisior's mini-manual (Box 19)
        - Taino Ann Street Project (Box 20)
        - Task Force (Box 20)
        - Task Force on Aging (Box 20)
        - Three year advisory plan member letters of thankyou (Box 20)
        - Three year housing advisory plan, 1983 (Box 20)
        - Three year Plan (Box 20)
        - Three year status report (Box 20)